<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">HamroPokhara</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    
    
    <string name="title_activity_begnas">
        Begnas
    </string>
    <string name="begnas">
         When the night curtains the environment the moon and the stars lighten the earth and there remains Begnas Lake reflecting the nature. The sky descends to kiss the lake, freshwater, and peaceful lake
   Begnas lake is situated 193 km northeast from Prithivi Highway and extends 28 10 26.2 N to 84 5 50.4 E. It covers an area of 3.73 sq.km (373 hector) and occupies 4.7% of Lekhnath Municipality. It is 7.5 to 10.6m deep. The rivers flowing through its chest are maintaining the greenery of the khudi , Syankhudi and Talbesi as well.
The lake has been protected by the nature itself. There are the majestic hills surrounding it on three sides and at the other, people amaze viewing the beauty. The Himalayas also grain at its charm. One can entertain by boating, sightseeing and Horse riding. Even a trekking route is developed in its periphery.  
        
    </string>
    <string name="Send">Send</string>
    <string name="lake">
        Lake side named after Phewa Lake is also attraction for many tourists. It is situated 28 12 5 N to 83 56 50 E and is in south of pokhara valley. Its primary inflows are Harpan and Phirke Khola. It has a catchment area of 122.53 km sq. its maximum length is 4 km (2.5 mile) and maximum depth is 24 km (79 Ft). It has a surface are of 5.32 km sq. It’s an average depth of 8.6m (28 Ft) and water volume of 0.046 km (0.011 cubic millimeters). There is a Phewa Power House at a distance of 1.5 km (0.9 mile) from southern part of Phewa Lake.
Lake is stream-fed but a dam regulates the water reserve so it is called as semi-natural freshwater lake and also the second largest lake country and largest in the Pokhara valley. The site is renowned for the reflection of Mount Macchapuchre, on the lake along with Mt. Annapurna and Mt. Dhaulagiri. Annapurna range on the north is only about 28 km (linear distance) away from the lake. Boat trip is also foremost attraction. Paddling out into the middle of lake is a nice way to spend.
The lush Rani Ban (Queen Forest) gives the still water a deep emerald hue. One can entertain by walking or cycling around the lake shore. World Peace Pagoda also afforts heavenly views over lake and mountains beyond.
    </string>
    <string name="sarangkot">     Sarangkot is a village inside pokhara valley which is famous from the tourism point of view.It is located on a mountain ridge having the altitude of 1592 m with the beautiful view of Himalaya range view. Sarangkot is famous for landscape and paragliding. The great view of Annapurna range can be seen from this place. The southern part consists of Dhaulagiri where from the southern part, the whole pokhara valley is seen and the view of Phewa Lake can be seen to the north-western part. Paragliding in Sarangkot can be a truly wonderful and fulfilling experience for the adventure seeker. </string>
    <string name="Barahi">It is the important religious monument inside pokhara. It is located on an island in Phew Lake. The two storied pagoda is devoted to boar manifestation of Ajima which represents the female force Shakti. The devotees will be found, mostly on Saturday for their prayer. </string>
    <string name="museum">While in Pokhara make it a point to visit the International Mountain Museum (IMM) that records, documents, exhibits and chronicles the past and the present development of mountains and mountaineering activities in the world. Built by Nepal Mountaineering Association (NMA), much support was received from various mountaineering clubs and associations as well as individual donors from around the world. The museum primarily provides information and exhibits everything related to Man, Mountain and Mountain activities from around the world.
IMM situated in Pokhara was opened on February 5, 2004. The Museum is spread over a total floor area of 4,242 sq meters on 12.5 acres of land. The museum contains three main exhibitions halls - Hall of Great Himalayas, Hall of Fame and Hall of World Mountains. It also contains models of famous peaks, mannequins of famous mountaineers, culture and lifestyle of mountain people, flora and fauna including geology. The museum has been built with the theme of man, mountains and mountaineering. The museum also has model Nepali houses constructed in its premises.</string>
    <string name="mahendra"></string>
    <string name="bat">This cave is located a little far form the Mahendra cave in the west .This cave was also discovered by the owner of the land – a farmer in the year 2040.Though the entrance is quite narrow but the inner part of the cave is wide enough. The images of the elephant tusk, gods and goddess have been craved on the inner walls of the cave.

This cave is 150 meter long, 25feet high and of the shape of “U”. This cave is famous for the bats and gives shelter to more than 15 thousand bats of different species. This cave needs to be advertised more for its development. It can be a nice picnic spot.</string>
    <string name="binda">Bindhyabasini Temple is also one of the most popular and well known temple in Pokhara.It is situated in the laps of Machhapuchhare and Annapurna ranges.This temple lies in the north of Pokhara. This temple is 3000 ft above from the sea level. You can get a fabulous view of Pokhara city and the Himalayas from this temple.The fragrance of the scented “Dhup” and refreshing air can keep anyone spellbound.

This temple originated when the Goddess “Bhawani “ told king khadag Bum Malla to establish her statue in Bindhyachal hill.This temple was established in B.S 1845 since then this goddess is worshipped daily.Even the tourists visits at least once there. This temple is one of the most important holy places for the Hindu people.The government has even printed its stamp with the picture of the temple in the year 2045.</string>
    <string name="intro">    Pokhara is the Sub-Metropolitan city which has more than 200000 inhabitants. It lies in 28.25°N, 83.99°E, 198 km west of Kathmandu. It is the 3rd largest city of Nepal. The climate is around 15 degree in winter and around 35 degree in summer. It is also called as cherrapunji of Nepal. It has the best weather between October and April.
It is the starting point for the trek for ABC (Annapurna Base Camp). It has the stunning panoramic views of Mountains. Once, pokhara used to be the trade route between India and Tibet. It is the place of Magars, Guungs, farmers and warriors who are known as Gorkha soldiers these days. The lke view and the magnificence of Himalayas which rise behind them make a symbol of peace and magic. So, this place is not only the starting point of trek, but also popular for the place to spend the holiday with the natural beauty.</string>
<string name="gup">Extending 28. 14” 28” North latitude to 83. 57” 13.4 last longitude, there lies the longest and attractive cane in south Asia; Gupteshwor Cave. It was formally established in 1994-01-01 as the religious and tourist destination. It lies 722m above the sea levels. Nearby the entrance there are amazing and natural picture of Lord Shiva, Prabati, Naag, Ganesh and Mouse. This reflects the religious important of the place. Inside the cave, there lies a temple with a huge stalagmite worshipped as Shiva Linga. This art is also praiseworthy.
Within the distance of 100m from the cave, i.e. bottom of Davi’s fall, one can see illumination of Limestone and mesmerizing scene of the water fall of Devi’s fall. The thundering of the water blows the mind away. The water vapor above the water seems to be breath taking. The water drops falling from the foot of the cave adds to the beauty of the cave. The declaration as the longest cave in the South Asia by Archaeologist is a matter of pride to all South Asians.
    
</string>
    <string name="Feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="santi">The pagoda is a massive Buddhist stupa and is situated on top of a hill on the southern shore of Phewa lake. Besides being an impressive sight in itself, the shrine is a great vantage point which offers spectacular views of the Annapurna range and Pokhara city. You can get there by crossing the lake by boat and then hiking up the hill.</string>
    <string name="getmap">Get Map</string>
    <string name="showdir"> Show Direction</string>
    <string name="title_activity_intro">Introduction</string>
    <string name="title_activity_barahi">Barahi Temple</string>
    <string name="title_activity_binda">Bindabasini</string>
    <string name="title_activity_museum">International Mountain Museum</string>
    <string name="title_activity_mahendra">Mahendra Cave</string>
    <string name="title_activity_bat">Bat Cave</string>
    <string name="title_activity_shanti">Shanti Stupa</string>
    <string name="title_activity_davis">Davis Fall</string>
    <string name="title_activity_gup">Gupteshwor Cave</string>
    <string name="title_activity_send_feed">SendFeed</string>
    <string name="title_activity_feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="title_activity_lake">Lakeside</string>
   <string name="sarang">Sarangkot</string>
    <string name="title_activity_splash">HamroPokhara</string>
    <string name="title_activity_showmap">Showmap</string>

</resources>